

// title of the MOD that appears on the Steam Workshop (limited to 128 characters)
Title: Cataclysm Remastered 1.3.1
// 1.3

// tags must be individual words separated by spaces.
Tags: homeworld ship space cataclysm somtaaw kuun-lan kuun lan kiith somtaaw beast HWC HomeworldRM HWRM

// gametype is the type of game this MOD is designed for and can be any of: "HW1Classic", "HW2Classic", or "HomeworldRM" (without the double quotes) separated by spaces
GameType: HomeworldRM

// modtype is the type of mod for the game and can be any one of: "MOD", "Locale", "Badges", or "Cursors"
ModType: MOD

// bigfilename is the file name you want to use for your .big file (this should be a single word with no spaces).
BigFilename: cataclysm.big

// WorkshopID is the Steam Workshop item number assigned to this item when you first create it.
// This should be 0 by default before you create your Workshop item and the Workshop Tool will
// set it to the Workshop Item number.  DO NOT modify this number once you have created a Workshop
// item.  It will be used to update the workshop item when you make changes to your MOD later on.  
WorkshopID: 416844570

//477426048 // TEST ?

// 416844570 // Main mod ?

// description that will appear on the Steam Workshop for this item
Description:

Welcome to Cataclysm Remastered! 

This mod is an in-progress community effort to bring HW Cataclysm into the new Remastered engine and the HWRM collection. 

Currently includes multiplayer / player vs CPU as Somtaaw, Beast or any vanilla race. Campaign levels coming soon! 

//Add [code]-mpbeta[/code] in the command-line parameters in the mod page to enable multiplayer.
No Build Limits: http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=472548772 
No Unit Caps: http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=485998120 
Alternate Hypserspace Effect (by HarbingerDawn): http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=469364176 


Most ship models are ported from the HWU HW2 mod, but some are modified HWRM models, or ported directly from Cataclysm. 
Weapons & FX are a mix of HWU & HWRM. 
Music / sounds are a direct port from Cataclysm. 

Thanks to LeviathansWrath, HWU team, 23-Down, and Taltharius for your help. 

v1.3.1:
-Stats balancing
-Fixed Cataclysm Remastered game mode
-Fixed incorrect audio (ambient noise, speech) for some ships and main menu music
-Fixed missing ship icons
-Changed Somtaaw capital attack strategy
-Fixed Kushan starting fleet bug
-Added Beast worker animations
-Replaced somtaaw & beast multibeam fire effects with full ion beams


v1.3: 
-Major changes for compatibility with the upcoming (add-on, beta) campaign mod. (Will release updates as missions are created).
-Preliminary Beast ship command sounds
-Added multiplayer button to main menu (no need for -mpbeta)
-Minor UI improvements
-Minor fixes for Somtaaw starting ships command & status sounds


